Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG.42.5
New York University Archives
- Series I: Exhibition Files, 1961-2004
  - Gerhard Richter -- Reviews (1 of 2), 1990 March-1995 July; cuid2949 (Box I:11, Folder 35)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Reviews (2 of 2), 1990 April-1995 July; cuid2950 (Box I:11, Folder 36)
  - Barbara Strasen, 1990 February-May; cuid2951 (Box I:11, Folder 37)
  - Paysage Demoralise: Landscape at the End of the Century -- Condition, 1990 May; cuid2952 (Box I:11, Folder 38)
  - Paysage Demoralise -- Press Release and Publicity, 1990 April; cuid2953 (Box I:11, Folder 39)
  - Paysage Demoralise -- Press, 1990 June; cuid2954 (Box I:11, Folder 40)
  - Paysage Demoralise -- Helen Chadwick, 1987-1990; cuid2955 (Box I:11, Folder 41)
  - Paysage Demoralise -- Graeme Murray Gallery/John Weber, Findlay, Goldsworthy, Cooper, 1987 August-1990 April; cuid2956 (Box I:11, Folder 42)
  - Paysage Demoralise -- Miscellaneous, 1987-1990; cuid2957 (Box I:11, Folder 43)
  - Peter Sebok -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Paysage Demoralise, 1 of 2), 1989; cuid2958 (Box I:11, Folder 44)
  - Peter Sebok -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Paysage Demoralise, 2 of 2), 1989-1992; cuid2959 (Box I:11, Folder 45)
  - Against Nature: Japanese Art in the Eighties -- Proposal, 1987-1988; cuid2960 (Box I:11, Folder 46)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Catalogue and Exhibit Roundtable Discussion, Circa 1989-1990; cuid2961 (Box I:11, Folder 47)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Labels, Circa 1989-1990; cuid2962 (Box I:11, Folder 48)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Color Xeroxes, Circa 1988-1990; cuid2963 (Box I:11, Folder 49)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Initial Schedule and Slide List, Circa 1989-1990; cuid2964 (Box I:11, Folder 50)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Installation, 1990; cuid2965 (Box I:11, Folder 51)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- John's Installation Notes, 1989 March-June; cuid2966 (Box I:11, Folder 52)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- General Unnamed Sheets (Lists), 1989 January-June; cuid2967 (Box I:11, Folder 53)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Dumb Type (1 of 2), 1988 June-1991 September; cuid2968 (Box I:11, Folder 54)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Dumb Type (2 of 2), 1988 July-1991 April; cuid2969 (Box I:11, Folder 55)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Dumbtype Correspondence, 1989 September-October; cuid2970 (Box I:11, Folder 56)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Dumb Type "PH" VHS, 1990; cuid2971 (Box I:12, Folder 1)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Press Releases, 1990 August 16; cuid2972 (Box I:12, Folder 2)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Press Photos Information, 1989 July-1991 January; cuid2973 (Box I:12, Folder 3)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Toshikatu Endo, 1987-1990; cuid2974 (Box I:12, Folder 4)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Shoko Maemoto, 1990 January; cuid2975 (Box I:12, Folder 5)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Masami Teraoka, 1990; cuid2976 (Box I:12, Folder 6)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Noboru Tsubaki, 1986; cuid2977 (Box I:12, Folder 7)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Press, 1988-1990; cuid2978 (Box I:12, Folder 8)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Press Information, 1989 January-June; cuid2979 (Box I:12, Folder 9)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Akron Art Museum Press, 1989 July-December; cuid2980 (Box I:12, Folder 10)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Boston Press, 1989 December; cuid2981 (Box I:12, Folder 11)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Grey Gallery Press (1 of 2), 1990 June-October; cuid2982 (Box I:12, Folder 12)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Grey Gallery Press (2 of 2), 1990 September-1991 February; cuid2983 (Box I:12, Folder 13)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- San Francisco Press, 1989 March-July; cuid2984 (Box I:12, Folder 14)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Reviews and Notices, 1988 June-1990 August; cuid2985 (Box I:12, Folder 15)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Akron Art Museum, 1989 September-October; cuid2986 (Box I:12, Folder 16)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Contemporary Art Museum, Houston (Miscellaneous), 1990 October-December; cuid2987 (Box I:12, Folder 17)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Seattle Art Museum, 1990 March-May; cuid2988 (Box I:12, Folder 18)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Yasumasa Morimura, 1991 September-1992 April; cuid2989 (Box I:12, Folder 19)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Japan Society News, 1988 March-November; cuid2990 (Box I:12, Folder 20)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Miscellaneous Artist and Exhibit Material, 1986-1990; cuid2991 (Box I:12, Folder 21)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Miscellaneous Clippings (1 of 2), 1987 April-1989 July; cuid2992 (Box I:12, Folder 22)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Miscellaneous Clippings (2 of 2), 1983 June-1988 November; cuid2993 (Box I:12, Folder 23)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Miscellaneous Printed Material (1 of 2), 1983-1988; cuid2994 (Box I:12, Folder 24)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Miscellaneous Printed Material (2 of 2), 1958-1988; cuid2995 (Box I:12, Folder 25)
  - The Greeks and the Sea (Small Gallery, Nov. 12-20, 1990), cuid2996 (Box I:12, Folder 26)
  - Mabou Mines -- Preliminary Work, Circa 1980-1991; cuid2997 (Box I:12, Folder 27)
  - Mabou Mines -- Installation, 1990 October-1991 January; cuid2998 (Box I:12, Folder 28)
  - Mabou Mines -- Drafts, Labels and Other Miscellaneous, 1976-1991; cuid2999 (Box I:12, Folder 29)
  - Mabou Mines -- Video Sleeve, 1990; cuid3000 (Box I:12, Folder 30)
  - Mabou Mines -- Press (1 of 2), 1980 December-1990 December; cuid3001 (Box I:12, Folder 31)
  - Mabou Mines -- Press (2 of 2), 1990 May; cuid3002 (Box I:12, Folder 32)
  - Tom Wolf and Ken Chu (Small Gallery/WSW), Circa 1990-1991; cuid3003 (Box I:12, Folder 33)
  - Mark Wallinger (Capital) -- Installation, 1990-1991; cuid3004 (Box I:12, Folder 34)
  - Mark Wallinger (Capital) -- Press, 1991 January-February; cuid3005 (Box I:12, Folder 35)
  - Mark Wallinger (Capital) -- Miscellaneous, Circa 1990-1991; cuid3006 (Box I:12, Folder 36)
  - Minnette Lehmann, 1988 January-1991 January; cuid3007 (Box I:12, Folder 37)
  - Permanent Collection, Circa 1990-1991; cuid3008 (Box I:12, Folder 38)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Checklists, 1991; cuid3009 (Box I:12, Folder 39)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Artists, 1990-1992; cuid3010 (Box I:12, Folder 40)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Artists CV's, 1991; cuid3011 (Box I:12, Folder 41)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Rasheed Araeen, 1991 June; cuid3012 (Box I:12, Folder 42)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Rebecca Belmore, Circa 1990-1991; cuid3013 (Box I:12, Folder 43)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Nadine Chan, 1991 January-1992 October; cuid3014 (Box I:12, Folder 44)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Albert Chong, 1991 June-November; cuid3015 (Box I:12, Folder 45)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Allan DeSouza, Circa 1991-1993; cuid3016 (Box I:12, Folder 46)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Jamelie Hassan, 1991 February-1993 May; cuid3017 (Box I:12, Folder 47)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Mona Hatoum, 1990 January-1993 April; cuid3018 (Box I:12, Folder 48)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Roshini Kempadoo, 1991 January-July; cuid3019 (Box I:12, Folder 49)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Glenn Ligon/Emily Fisher Landay, 1991 June-1992; cuid3020 (Box I:12, Folder 50)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Whitfield Lovell, 1990 December-Circa 1992; cuid3021 (Box I:12, Folder 51)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Lani Maestro, 1991 February-1993 April; cuid3022 (Box I:12, Folder 52)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Lillian Mulero, 1990 December-1991 January; cuid3023 (Box I:12, Folder 53)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Ming Mur-Ray, 1990 December-1992 April; cuid3024 (Box I:12, Folder 54)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Keith Piper, 1990 January-October; cuid3025 (Box I:12, Folder 55)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Ingrid Pollard, 1990 November-1992 October; cuid3026 (Box I:12, Folder 56)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Donald Rodney/Art Council Collection, 1991 July-December; cuid3027 (Box I:12, Folder 57)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Yinka Shonibare, 1990 October 19; cuid3028 (Box I:12, Folder 58)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Simmons/Janelle Reiring Metro Pictures, 1989 December-1990 April; cuid3029 (Box I:12, Folder 59)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Black Artists File, 1985-1990; cuid3030 (Box I:13, Folder 1)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists, 1989-1990; cuid3031 (Box I:13, Folder 2)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists (In Show), 1985 April-1991 September; cuid3032 (Box I:13, Folder 3)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists (Not Included), 1990 June-December; cuid3033 (Box I:13, Folder 4)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists (Mulero), 1991; cuid3034 (Box I:13, Folder 5)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists (Gary Simmons), 1989 December-1990 August; cuid3035 (Box I:13, Folder 6)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists (Glenn Ligon), 1991 July 29; cuid3036 (Box I:13, Folder 7)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- English Artists, 1988-1991 October; cuid3037 (Box I:13, Folder 8)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- English Artists (Rasheed Araaen), 1990 November-1992 October; cuid3038 (Box I:13, Folder 9)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- English Artists (Roshini Kempadoo), 1990-1991; cuid3039 (Box I:13, Folder 10)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Canadian Artists (Jamilie Hassan), 1984-1990; cuid3040 (Box I:13, Folder 11)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Canadian Artists (Lani Maestro), 1988-1991; cuid3041 (Box I:13, Folder 12)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Canadian Artists (Rejections), 1990-1991; cuid3042 (Box I:13, Folder 13)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Toronto/Halifax Notes, Lists and Other Miscellaneous, 1990-1991; cuid3043 (Box I:13, Folder 14)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- English Artists (Keith Piper), 1990 August-1991 January; cuid3044 (Box I:13, Folder 15)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- English Artists (Donald Rodney), 1990; cuid3045 (Box I:13, Folder 16)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Canadian Art, 1988-Circa 1991; cuid3046 (Box I:13, Folder 17)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Floor Plan, 1991; cuid3047 (Box I:13, Folder 18)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Research, Undated; cuid3048 (Box I:13, Folder 19)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Research (2 of 2), 1987-1990; cuid3049 (Box I:13, Folder 20)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Catalogue, Circa 1989-1991; cuid3050 (Box I:13, Folder 21)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Catalogue (Maharaj Essay Draft), 1990-1991; cuid3051 (Box I:13, Folder 22)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Catalogue, 1991; cuid3052 (Box I:13, Folder 23)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Text, Circa 1990-1991; cuid3053 (Box I:13, Folder 24)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Text for II, Circa 1990-1991; cuid3054 (Box I:13, Folder 25)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Programming for II, Circa 1990-1991; cuid3055 (Box I:13, Folder 26)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- July 1990 London Research (1 of 2), 1988-1991; cuid3056 (Box I:13, Folder 27)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- July 1990 London Research (2 of 2), 1988-1991; cuid3057 (Box I:13, Folder 28)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Installation, 1991; cuid3058 (Box I:13, Folder 29)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Checklist, Installation and Packing Instructions, 1990-1993; cuid3059 (Box I:13, Folder 30)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Materials for Venue Book, 1991-1992; cuid3060 (Box I:13, Folder 31)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Press, 1991 March-1993 January; cuid3061 (Box I:13, Folder 32)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Duke Press, 1993 January; cuid3062 (Box I:13, Folder 33)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Madison Art Center, 1991 March-1992 August; cuid3063 (Box I:13, Folder 34)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Madison Press Materials, 1991-1992; cuid3064 (Box I:13, Folder 35)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Miami Press Materials, 1992 June-July; cuid3065 (Box I:13, Folder 36)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- MFA Press Materials (Boston), 1991-1992; cuid3066 (Box I:13, Folder 37)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Walker Art Center Press, 1992; cuid3067 (Box I:13, Folder 38)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Notes and Miscellaneous Items, 1990 July-1991 March; cuid3068 (Box I:13, Folder 39)
  - Luis Caballero, 1982-1991; cuid3069 (Box I:13, Folder 40)
  - Hope Sandrow, 1991; cuid3070 (Box I:13, Folder 41)
  - Hope Sandrow -- General Idea, 1991; cuid3071 (Box I:13, Folder 42)
  - General Idea, Circa 1991; cuid3072 (Box I:13, Folder 43)
  - Caballero/Sandrow/General Idea, 1991 May-October; cuid3073 (Box I:13, Folder 44)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Checklists, 1990-1991; cuid3074 (Box I:13, Folder 45)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Installation (1 of 2), 1991; cuid3075 (Box I:13, Folder 46)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Installation (2 of 2), 1991; cuid3076 (Box I:13, Folder 47)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Research and Exhibit Material (1 of 3), 1988-1991; cuid3077 (Box I:13, Folder 48)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Research and Exhibit Material (2 of 3), 1990-1991; cuid3078 (Box I:14, Folder 1)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Research and Exhibit Material (3 of 3), 1985-1991; cuid3079 (Box I:14, Folder 2)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Questions, 1988; cuid3080 (Box I:14, Folder 3)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Tour Materials, Circa 1990-1991; cuid3081 (Box I:14, Folder 4)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Public Relations, Circa 1983-1991; cuid3082 (Box I:14, Folder 5)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Press, 1991 July-September; cuid3083 (Box I:14, Folder 6)
  - Yasuzo Nojima Exhibition -- Plan and Proposal, 1989-1990; cuid3084 (Box I:14, Folder 7)
  - Yasuzo Nojima Exhibit -- Captions, CIrca 1991-1992; cuid3085 (Box I:14, Folder 8)
  - Yasuzo Nojima Exhibit -- Press, 1991 November 26; cuid3086 (Box I:14, Folder 9)
  - Aids Bottle Project, 1991; cuid3087 (Box I:14, Folder 10)
  - Tomie Arai (Window Installation), 1991 September-December; cuid3088 (Box I:14, Folder 11)
  - Michael Andrews -- Lists, Labels, Text and Other Miscellaneous, 1986-1991; cuid3089 (Box I:14, Folder 12)
  - Michael Andrews -- Printed Reseach, 1980-1991; cuid3090 (Box I:14, Folder 13)
  - Michael Andrews -- Press, 1992 January-1995 July; cuid3091 (Box I:14, Folder 14)
  - Spinster's Tale (Windows) -- Lindsey Walt, 1991 November-1992 June; cuid3092 (Box I:14, Folder 15)
  - A Day Without Art -- 1990, cuid3093 (Box I:14, Folder 16)
  - A Day Without Art -- 1991, cuid3094 (Box I:14, Folder 17)
  - A Day Without Art -- 1992, cuid3095 (Box I:14, Folder 18)
  - A Day Without Art -- 1993, cuid3096 (Box I:14, Folder 19)
  - A Day Without Art -- 1994, cuid3097 (Box I:14, Folder 20)
  - A Day Without Art -- Visual Aids Ribbon Project, 1989-1992; cuid3098 (Box I:14, Folder 21)
  - A Day Without Art -- Press, 1989-1993; cuid3099 (Box I:14, Folder 22)
  - A Day Without Art -- Publicity Packet, 1989-1991; cuid3100 (Box I:14, Folder 23)
  - Elaine Reichek: Native Intelligence -- Biography and Slides, Circa 1990-1992; cuid3101 (Box I:14, Folder 24)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Catalogue, Circa 1991-1992; cuid3102 (Box I:14, Folder 25)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Errata Sheets, Undated; cuid3103 (Box I:14, Folder 26)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Installation, Circa 1991-1993; cuid3104 (Box I:14, Folder 27)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Lists and Installation, Circa 1991-1992; cuid3105 (Box I:14, Folder 28)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Condition, 1990-1993; cuid3106 (Box I:14, Folder 29)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Press and Photo Material, 1989 February-1993 May; cuid3107 (Box I:14, Folder 30)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Drafts, Notes and Other Miscellaneous, Circa 1989-1993; cuid3108 (Box I:14, Folder 31)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Schedule (Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art), 1992 November-1993 April; cuid3109 (Box I:14, Folder 32)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Western Washington University, 1992 October-1993 April; cuid3110 (Box I:14, Folder 33)
  - Lily van der Stokker (Small Gallery), 1989 October-1992 March; cuid3111 (Box I:14, Folder 34)
  - Arne Svenson (Windows), 1989 August-1992 March; cuid3112 (Box I:14, Folder 35)
  - Opulent Past -- Artifact Copies (1 of 2), 1992; cuid3113 (Box I:14, Folder 36)
  - Opulent Past -- Artifact Copies (2 of 2), 1992; cuid3114 (Box I:14, Folder 37)
  - Opulent Past -- Catalogue, 1992; cuid3115 (Box I:14, Folder 38)
  - Opulent Past -- Installation, 1992 April-May; cuid3116 (Box I:14, Folder 39)
  - Opulent Past -- Invitations, 1992; cuid3117 (Box I:14, Folder 40)
  - Opulent Past -- Press, 1992 June-1993 November; cuid3118 (Box I:14, Folder 41)
  - John Kohring (Small Gallery), 1990 October-1992 May; cuid3119 (Box I:14, Folder 42)
  - Michael Richards (Windows), 1992 February-December; cuid3120 (Box I:14, Folder 43)
  - Camera As Weapon, 1992; cuid3121 (Box I:14, Folder 44)
  - Camera As Weapon -- Press, 1992 September-November; cuid3122 (Box I:14, Folder 45)
  - Adrian Piper: Decide Who You Are, 1991 August-1992 July; cuid3123 (Box I:14, Folder 46)
  - Adrian Piper -- Magazine, 1993 September-October; cuid3124 (Box I:14, Folder 47)
  - Jeff Gates (Windows), 1989 April-1992 August; cuid3125 (Box I:14, Folder 48)
  - Australian AIDS Posters, 1992 September-1996 December; cuid3126 (Box I:14, Folder 49)
  - Hugh Steers (Small Gallery), 1990-1992; cuid3127 (Box I:14, Folder 50)
  - Gotscho -- Correspondence, 1991 October-1993 January; cuid3128 (Box I:15, Folder 1)
  - Gotscho -- Biographies, Circa 1992-1993; cuid3129 (Box I:15, Folder 2)
  - Gotscho -- Exhibit [Installation], Circa 1991-1993; cuid3130 (Box I:15, Folder 3)
  - Gotscho -- Public Relations, 1992 April-1993 March; cuid3131 (Box I:15, Folder 4)
  - Joshua Neustein, 1992-1993; cuid3132 (Box I:15, Folder 5)
  - Joshua Neustein -- Press Kit, 1992 August-November; cuid3133 (Box I:15, Folder 6)
  - Jane Gifford (Small Gallery), 1992-1993; cuid3134 (Box I:15, Folder 7)
  - Alan Michelson (Windows), 1993; cuid3135 (Box I:15, Folder 8)
  - NetherArt -- Biographies, Undated; cuid3136 (Box I:15, Folder 9)
  - NetherArt -- Correspondence, 1992 July-1993 September; cuid3137 (Box I:15, Folder 10)
  - NetherArt -- Exhibition, 1992-1993; cuid3138 (Box I:15, Folder 11)
  - NetherArt -- Public Relations, 1993 March-July; cuid3139 (Box I:15, Folder 12)
  - NetherArt -- Registration, 1990 November-1993 August; cuid3140 (Box I:15, Folder 13)
  - Other Borders -- Biographies, 1991-1993; cuid3141 (Box I:15, Folder 14)
  - Other Borders -- Correspondence, 1992 September-1993 May; cuid3142 (Box I:15, Folder 15)
  - Other Borders -- Exhibition, 1993; cuid3143 (Box I:15, Folder 16)
  - Other Borders -- Public Relations, 1991 May-1993 May; cuid3144 (Box I:15, Folder 17)
  - Other Borders -- Registration, 1993 February-1994 March; cuid3145 (Box I:15, Folder 18)
  - The Museum in the Gallery -- Exhibition, Circa 1993; cuid3146 (Box I:15, Folder 19)
  - The Museum in the Gallery -- Public Relations, 1993 May-July; cuid3147 (Box I:15, Folder 20)
  - Matthew Benedict (Windows), 1993 March-May; cuid3148 (Box I:15, Folder 21)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Biographies, 1992 October-November; cuid3149 (Box I:15, Folder 22)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Correspondence (1 of 2), 1992 February-1994 October; cuid3150 (Box I:15, Folder 23)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Correspondence (2 of 2), 1990-1994; cuid3151 (Box I:15, Folder 24)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Exhibition, 1993; cuid3152 (Box I:15, Folder 25)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Public Relations, 1993-1994; cuid3153 (Box I:15, Folder 26)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Registration, 1993 July-1994 November; cuid3154 (Box I:15, Folder 27)
  - Bill Jacobson (Small Gallery), 1993; cuid3155 (Box I:15, File 28)
  - Jim Hodges (Windows), 1993-1995; cuid3156 (Box I:15, Folder 29)
  - Anyone in New York -- Biography, 1993 October; cuid3157 (Box I:15, Folder 30)
  - Anyone in New York -- Correspondence, 1993 May-December; cuid3158 (Box I:15, Folder 31)
  - Anyone in New York -- Exhibition, Circa 1992-1993; cuid3159 (Box I:15, Folder 32)
  - Anyone in New York -- Public Relations, 1993 June-December; cuid3160 (Box I:15, Folder 33)
  - Brief Encounters (Small Gallery) -- Registration, 1993 October-1994 January; cuid3161 (Box I:15, Folder 34)
  - Simon Patterson (Small Gallery), 1993 August-1994 April; cuid3162 (Box I:15, Folder 35)
  - Lydia Schouten (Windows), 1993 January-November; cuid3163 (Box I:15, Folder 36)
  - Art About Aids -- Biographies, 1989-Circa 1994; cuid3164 (Box I:15, Folder 37)
  - Art About Aids -- Correspondence, 1989 February-1993 December; cuid3165 (Box I:15, Folder 38)
  - Art About Aids -- Exhibition, Circa 1993-1994; cuid3166 (Box I:15, Folder 39)
  - Art About Aids -- Public Relations (1 of 3), 1992 January-1994 July; cuid3167 (Box I:15, Folder 40)
  - Art About Aids -- Public Relations (2 of 3), 1991 August-1994 February; cuid3168 (Box I:16, Folder 1)
  - Art About Aids -- Public Relations (3 of 3), 1993 February-1994 April; cuid3169 (Box I:16, Folder 2)
  - Art About Aids -- Registration, 1991 March-1994 April; cuid3170 (Box I:16, Folder 3)
  - Visual Aids (Small Gallery), Circa 1993-1994; cuid3171 (Box I:16, Folder 4)
  - Joseph Stashkevetch (Windows), CIrca 1993-1994; cuid3172 (Box I:16, Folder 5)
  - Todd Watts -- Biographies, 1994; cuid3173 (Box I:16, Folder 6)
  - Todd Watts -- Correspondence, 1990 February-1994 June; cuid3174 (Box I:16, Folder 7)
  - Todd Watts -- Exhibit Catalog, 1993-1994; cuid3175 (Box I:20, Folder 33)
  - Todd Watts -- Exhibition, Circa 1993-1994; cuid3176 (Box I:16, Folder 8)
  - Todd Watts -- Registration, 1993 December-1994 May; cuid3177 (Box I:16, Folder 10)
  - Three Women in Black (Windows), 1994; cuid3178 (Box I:16, Folder 11)
  - 1969: A Year Revisited -- Correspondence, 1994 April-June; cuid3179 (Box I:16, Folder 12)
  - 1969: A Year Revisited -- Exhibition, Circa 1992-1994; cuid3180 (Box I:16, Folder 13)
  - 1969: A Year Revisited -- Public Relations, 1969 January-1994 July; cuid3181 (Box I:16, Folder 14)
  - 1969: A Year Revisited -- Registration, 1994 February-August; cuid3182 (Box I:16, Folder 15)
  - Rob Wynne (Windows), 1993 October-1994 July; cuid3183 (Box I:16, Folder 16)
  - Arne Svenson (Small Gallery), 1994; cuid3184 (Box I:16, Folder 17)
  - Willie Doherty -- Biographies, 1992 November; cuid3185 (Box I:16, Folder 18)
  - Willie Doherty -- Correspondence, 1992 March-1994 August; cuid3186 (Box I:16, Folder 19)
  - Willie Doherty -- Public Relations, 1990 October-1994 October; cuid3187 (Box I:16, Folder 20)
  - Willie Doherty -- Registration, 1994 March-December; cuid3188 (Box I:16, Folder 21)
  - John Defazio (Small Gallery), 1993-1994; cuid3189 (Box I:16, Folder 22)
  - Rene Santos -- Biographies, 1994 September; cuid3190 (Box I:16, Folder 23)
  - Rene Santos -- Correspondence, 1982-1995 July; cuid3191 (Box I:16, Folder 24)
  - Rene Santos -- Exhibition, Circa 1992-1994; cuid3192 (Box I:16, Folder 25)
  - Rene Santos -- Public Relations, 1994-1995; cuid3193 (Box I:16, Folder 26)
  - Rene Santos -- Registration (Miscellaneous Correspondence, Checklists, 1 of 2), Circa 1994-1995; cuid3194 (Box I:16, Folder 27)
  - Rene Santos -- Registration (Miscellaneous Correspondence, Checklists, 2 of 2), 1994 August-October; cuid3195 (Box I:16, Folder 28)
  - Rene Santos -- Registration (Packing List, Condition), 1994 September-December; cuid3196 (Box I:16, Folder 29)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Biographies, 1992-1994; cuid3197 (Box I:16, Folder 30)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Correspondence, 1993 May-1995 February; cuid3198 (Box I:16, Folder 31)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Exhibition, 1994-Circa 1995; cuid3199 (Box I:16, Folder 32)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Public Relations, 1994 January-1995 February; cuid3200 (Box I:16, Folder 33)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Registration, 1994 July-1995 April; cuid3201 (Box I:16, Folder 34)
  - Jason Reed (Small Gallery and Windows), 1994 December-1995 February; cuid3202 (Box I:16, Folder 35)
  - Ann Mandelbaum -- Biographies, Undated; cuid3203 (Box I:16, Folder 36)
  - Ann Mandelbaum -- Correspondence, 1994 January-October; cuid3204 (Box I:16, Folder 37)
  - Ann Mandelbaum -- Exhibition, Circa 1994-1995; cuid3205 (Box I:16, Folder 38)
  - Ann Mandelbaum -- Public Relations, 1994-1995; cuid3206 (Box I:16, Folder 39)